Everyone waits for the Mahadasha of Guru, the Mahadasha of Jupiter
because everyone feels
that the Mahadasha of Guru is coming, then
what can I say, there is a lot of positivity,
Guru is the most positive planet, he is a virtuous person,
Guru blesses you, gives you
guidance, says good things
about you, Guru
can never think bad or negative about anyone, so due to which everyone
waits for the Mahadasha of Guru, Jupiter and especially all the
astrologers, all the Pandit people,
they just say that the Mahadasha of your Guru is about to
start.  From there a
miracle is going to happen in your life.  Where will you
reach from where?  All
your Rajyoga will be activated in your life.  I don't know what all they
say.  But the thing is that
Guru Mahadasha does not go well for everyone.  Guru
Mahadasha is good.  For a lot of people.
But for those people like
Capricorn ascendant,
Jupiter Mahadasha is rarely good
because it is the lord of the 12th house.  Since Jupiter
is the lord of the third house, the
Mahadasha of Jupiter may not be good for some people.  It does
not happen very often even for Gemini people.  Why?  Because
for people with Gemini ascendant, they also become obstacles.
So many things happen here.   To know whether
a situation is good or bad, one usually has to
look at the results.  Nakshatra So Many
Things: Whether you know it or not, it doesn't matter.
We will make a series on Mahadasha to tell
how the Mahadasha of Jupiter is
for every ascendant.  So you will know
how it will go for your marriage.
But right now I want to talk about the thing
that we have already talked about the remedy for Rahu Mahadasha.  Right now
Guru is going well for you.
So how can we maintain this goodness
?  How can we keep it stable?  And secondly,
your Guru Mahadasha is not going well.
So how can we satisfy Jupiter a little bit?
We can do this one too.
So I am going to talk about all these things
in this video that
what can we do in the Mahadasha of Guru?
[Music]
I believe that if the Mahadasha of Guru is going well,
Guru gives exponential growth.
Guru is a multiplier.   If it is
good then we are going to multiply the good.
If it is bad then he is going to multiply the bad also.
So obviously
it is a disturbing thing that you have to see
that the Mahadasha of Jupiter has started.  Are you
multiplying positivity for yourself or are you
multiplying negativity?  So,
you have to do all these things carefully.
But now the Mahadasha of Jupiter is about to begin.   It is about to
begin.  He's the
owner of Sagittarius you have to see and he's the owner of Piscis.
And both are zodiac signs of religion.
Actually Pisces is the zodiac sign of salvation.  Pisces
is charitable.  Pisces talks a lot about spirituality.
And Sagittarius, the zodiac sign of Jupiter, is the Moolatrikona zodiac sign, it
tells you to take education by
staying with the Guru, to take education, to go to temples, it
tells you all these things, so in short, the
Guru has only spirituality and
knowledge.  So after the start of Guru's Mahadasha,
you have to do only one remedy.  I will
say two.  I have given the same remedy for everyone in the entire series.
But for this
I am going to give an extra tip to
everyone that the Mahadasha of Guru has started, so
please start two things.  One, you should recite some hymns daily.  Incorporate
some Scripture into your life.
Because the Guru
talks about the Scriptures.  So you can chant Gayatri Mantra daily from the Old Scriptures,
some verses from the Upanishads,
some verses from the Gita, anything
from Durga Saptashati, whatever you like from anywhere,
you feel it is right to chant it.  Be it any
mantra of Mahadev ji or mantra of Vishnu ji,
you should fix some time daily
that I am reading all these mantras
in the scriptures, reciting them
and go to far away temples, there is
a zodiac sign of Guru, Sagittarius, Sagittarius
says pilgrim, there is talk of pilgrimage,
pilgrimage means
going to the pilgrimage, like this Kumbh
bath was being discussed, what did everyone do, they
went to the pilgrimage.  Actually, I have taken a holy bath and
visited the pilgrimage site.  In this
way you should go on pilgrimage.  That means
you should go to old and far away temples.  Go
there and sing whatever praises you have in praise of God.
Now comes the
interesting remedy which I am going to
tell you all.  There is only one temple of Lord Brahma on the entire earth.
And the
universe has come from Brahma ji only.  His wife is
Goddess Saraswati.  He has all the knowledge.
Everything is there.  So when your Guru's
Mahadasha is about to start or Guru's
Mahadasha is going on, Antardasha is already going on.  The
Mahadasha of Jupiter lasts for a very long time.
Lasts up to 16 years.  So
when your Mahadasha of Guru is going on, it is starting.
You should visit Pushkar on a regular basis which is
in our Rajasthan.  It is a little further from Jaipur.
So you people,
in that temple of Pushkar, there is only one temple of Lord Brahma.
Go there.  You should go there and
offer prayers.  Meditate.  That is very very
important.  Meditate,
worship.  Visit the
temple of Lord Brahma.  There Pushkar is a writer.
You should worship there.  This is one thing
you should maintain.  And two things along with this,
do some scripture recitation daily
and visit far away temples.  One of those
temples you should visit every year is the
Pushkar temple.  Because of this,
Guru Jupiter will be satisfied with you.
So, the Guru multiplies the negativity in your life in such a
way that the
Guru has the power of understanding and
judgment.  When the Guru has knowledge, it becomes
easy to choose what is right and what is wrong.
Only knowledge tells you that this
horse is a horse and this donkey is a donkey.  So in the same
way when the knowledge reaches the level which the
Guru has.  Guru is the name itself.  He is the
one to deliver wisdom, just not knowledge wisdom, I am
talking very very high.  So
when you have knowledge,
you know which things are right and
which things are wrong for you, so you will have the
knowledge, the blessings of Jupiter will
come automatically or will come in some eternal way, one
thing is that not everyone
gets a Guru, right, Guru does not come in every person's life, some
people do not
come but some people are eternally driven,
meaning you automatically keep choosing the right things
in life, automatically
you are guided by the you know eternal power and
something, at least this thing will happen in your life.
If you have followed these two-three
remedies that I have told you, then
in the Mahadasha of Jupiter, your
thoughts, ideas and meditation, everything will be right
and the blessings of Lord Jupiter will also
come in your life.  So isn't this
interesting? For many interesting remedies
and predictions, keep watching the
direction and condition of Swastik Global.
[music]